Finding scorpions in the desert at night
is surprisingly easy.
All you need is an ultraviolet torch
because scorpions are
incredibly fluorescent.
Fluorescence means their
bodies absorb ultraviolet light
and reradiate it in the
visible part of the spectrum.
They glow this bright neon green color.
But scorpions aren't the
only animals that fluoresce.
Jellyfish, amphibians,
owls, and even platypus'
glow under ultraviolet light.
Part of this video is sponsored
by Capital One Shopping.
More about them at the end of the show.
I'm out here in the desert
near Bakersfield, California,
looking for scorpions with Carl Kloock,
a professor of biology
at Cal State Bakersfield.
He's been researching
scorpion fluorescence
for over a decade.
- If you have a black light
it's really pretty easy.
If they're there, you're
going to spot them.
- [Derek] Does he look
like he's in a posture
to like defend himself?
- [Carl] Yeah, he's not real happy.
- [Derek] Okay.
(man chuckling)
- [Carl] I'm going to grab my high-tech
scorpion catching equipment here.
It's a tongue depressor with
a yellow highlighter on it.
So it fluoresces in black light.
So you can see where it is.
- [Derek] Got it.
(man chuckling)
- [Carl] This technique is usually to put
the vial behind him,
then in front of him.
- [Derek] That was impressive.
All right. Should we give it a shot?
- [Carl] Just gently pokes him back in.
And they usually just kind of do a little
side crab walk back.
There you go, and just tilt it up.
- [Derek] Unbelievable.
(man chuckles)
Unbelievable.
All right. I'm going to get him.
But why are scorpions fluorescent?
- I've got about 12 hypotheses.
So you test them one at a time.
- [Derek] You've got
12 Hypotheses about why
the scorpions fluoresce?
- More like six actually,
I was being a little bit...
Almost all scorpions fluoresce.
I haven't seen it myself,
but some that live at living
caves they don't fluoresce
but it's only like one very small group.
All the other scorpions fluoresce.
One possibility is just,
this is a Relic Trait.
It's something they developed way back
when they first came out on
land and just haven't lost.
A chemical that has another function
that just happens to fluoresce.
There are plenty of
chemicals that fluoresce.
I mean, we have internal
bodily fluids that fluoresce.
And clearly those are
never exposed to UV light.
So the idea of having a function
for that fluorescence is kind of silly.
This fluoresce is about the
same color as a scorpion,
but clearly isn't a scorpion.
It's actually a rock.
The color is a little off.
- [Derek] But that is like, what is that?
- It's plastic from Walpole.
- [Derek] Huh.
You anted to know if the
scorpions were fluorescing
in order to attract insects.
- Right.
- [Narrator] So how did you test that?
- What I did was I used preserved
scorpions like these ones
and I took half of them and dip them in
UV blocking marine varnish
so they didn't fluoresce.
And then I just used basically flypaper
and took those things outside
and set them side by side
and then found the
number of flying insects
that were caught in each.
- [Derek] Okay.
- [Carl] So we were outside in moonlight
and I did the same experiment,
both under the new moon and the full moon.
And so what I found from that was
when there was a new moon,
there was no difference in the number
of insects caught by the fluorescent
and non-fluorescent scorpions.
But under the full moon,
there's nice, bright UV light
available there was a difference
and the ones that fluoresce
actually caught fewer insects.
- It seems kind of counterintuitive.
- So that tells me that
my hypothesis was wrong.
Which happens a lot.
Basically yeah, they're not using
their fluorescence to lure insects.
In fact, the fluorescence is
a bad thing for them in terms
of their ability to catch
flying insects, at least.
- Let me ask you this.
If you find that fluorescence
is counterproductive
for the scorpion in some way,
doesn't that indicate that there
has to be something useful?
- Exactly. There must be
something that counteracts that.
- Sort of negative.
- That negative, yeah.
Scorpions are really well
adapted for what they do.
One of the cool things
here is it scorpions
are actually able to
metabolize iron and nickel.
And in their pincer here
and on the tips of their claws,
they actually have basically
iron to strengthen that.
- [Derek] Iron and nickel
at the end of their tail?
- [Carl] Yeah. Yeah.
You can see like the color
here's a little bit different
and that's because of the iron.
- [Derek] That seems
very aggressive to me.
One of the main things
we're interested in here
is how they see.
So I've seen two of their eyes.
- [Carl] So, those are the
median eyes right there.
- [Derek] Those two dark spots.
- [Carl] Yeah. There's a cluster
of three eyes right there.
And of course on the other
side, so they're symmetrical.
So they have a total of eight eyes.
- Can they detect the light with parts of their body
它们可以用身体的一部分感受到光吗
that are not eyes?
如果不用眼睛的话
- Yeah. Actually they can.
是的，它们确实可以
- [Derek] In a 1968 experiment,
1968年，有人做了一个实验
researchers put scorpions in
half covered Petri dishes.
研究者们把蝎子放进遮住了一半的培养皿里面
Then they exposed them to bright
light and all the scorpions
然后将它们置于明亮光照下
quickly hid under the covered
part of the Petri dish.
所有的蝎子都迅速躲进了遮光的那一半区域
Then the researchers painted
over the eyes of the scorpions.
随后，他们又给蝎子的眼睛刷上油漆
So they couldn't see and
repeated the experiment.
这剥夺了蝎子的视力，接着他们重复了刚才的实验
But when they turned on
the light, 93% of the time,
但当他们开灯后，有93%的时间
the blinded scorpions still scuttled over
这些瞎掉的蝎子依然逃到
to the covered side.
没有光照的那一半
The finding was remarkable.
这个发现相当惊人
Scorpions don't need their eyes to detect light.
蝎子不需要用眼睛来探测光亮
They can sense it with their bodies.
它们用身体就能做到
- That showed that they have what's called
这表明，它们尾部有一种所谓的
an extra ocular light sense in their tail.
额外的光感器
So they can detect light with their tail.
所以它们可以用尾巴探测到光
They can't form images, they can't,
它们不能这样产生视觉
确实
but they can detect light.
但可以用来探测光
- The tail of a scorpion can detect light?
蝎子的尾巴可以用来探测光线？
- One hypothesis is that they use it
有一种猜测是，它们通过这种荧光
to communicate with one another.
来互相交流
The idea being that
they use it to determine
它们用荧光来
primarily whether or not
初步判断
another scorpion out there
其他的蝎子是否
is of the same species for mating.
和自己是同一个物种，可以交配
One fairly low probability hypothesis
还有种猜测，可能性相对低一些
is that they can use it as camouflage
它们把荧光当成迷彩
because they absorb UV light.
因为它们可以吸收紫外线
If they're sitting on another
surface that absorbs UV light
如果它们身处同样会吸收紫外线的物体表面
and you have an organism
that sees in the UV light
对于一些可以看到紫外线的动物
like some owls and
things like that can do,
比如猫头鹰之类的
they would tend to blend
in very nicely with that.
在它们眼中，蝎子很容易和环境混在一起
So it's a possibility,
所以这也是一种可能
but not that many organisms see in UV
但是没有那么多能看到紫外光的物种
and not that many that
eat scorpion, see in UV
而捕食蝎子的物种也鲜有能看到紫外光的
so it doesn't seem very likely.
所以这个假说似乎不大可能成立
- [Derek] You go for it.
你来抓这只蝎子
- [Carl] You want me to do it upclose?
要我靠上去吗？
- [Narrator] You do it.
行
- [Carl] Close.
快抓到了
Here you go. See?
搞定
能看到吗
There you go, wow.
就是这个 哇
- One of the ideas is
scorpions came out of the water
有种观点认为，蝎子离开水
from Silurian period long time ago.
是在志留纪时期，那是很久以前
And there was a lot
more UV just in sunlight
当时，太阳光里的紫外线强度比现在高得多
and things like that then,
because we didn't have
还有其它类似的辐射
因为那时候的地球并没有
an ozone layer, we didn't have, you know,
臭氧层，你知道的，那时候真没有
all these things that are
blocking UV in our atmosphere now.
现在的我们，全靠大气中的臭氧层阻挡紫外光
And so the one of the idea is that
于是就有了又一个假说
it actually acts as a sunscreen.
这种荧光实际上是防晒层
It's way to absorb those
damaging ultraviolet photons
是一种吸收有害紫外光的方式
and convert them away into something
同时将它们转化为其它能量
and basically keep them from
penetrating into the body
避免它们直接穿透身体
and causing damage.
并导致损伤
- [Derek] Go in your hole.
进去吧你
There you go.
抓到了
You got him.
抓到啦
- And then there have been some other ones
当然还有一些其他的猜想
that are a little bit more out there.
这些猜想有一点点奇怪
One of which being the one that I actually
其中一个，也是我
settled on at the end is that they use it
拿来压轴的这一个，就是，蝎子把荧光
as part of their sensory
system to detect the presence
当成感觉系统的一部分，用来探测
of light in the environment.
环境中光线的存在
So this was the later
experiment after I gave up
这个实验做得迟，是在我放弃最初的想法以后
on the initial idea that
said that didn't work.
那个想法否定了这一种可能
So, all I really did in
that one, very simple,
实验的操作非常简单
put a scorpion in each
one of these things here
把蝎子关进这种培养皿
and then put this under ultraviolet light
然后放在紫外灯下
and exposed it to ultraviolet light.
让它被紫外线照射
And so I measured how
long they spent exposed
我比较了它们暴露在外
versus unexposed and how many times
和躲起来的时间，同时还记录了
they went back and forth.
它们来回的次数
- [Derek] And you were testing scorpions
所以你在测试
that were fluorescent and not fluorescent.
有荧光的和没有荧光的蝎子
- [Carl] Right.
是的
So what I did with that was I developed
为了处理这些蝎子，我开发了一个技术
a technique to remove, or at least reduce
用来解除，或者至少减弱
the ability of scorpions to fluoresce
蝎子产生荧光的能力
simply by exposing them for long periods
只要将它们长时间
of time to ultraviolet light.
置于紫外光下
So basically, you're just
kind of taking the chemical
主要是为了在一定程度上去除
that is causing fluorescence
in their exoskeleton
蝎子外骨骼表面的荧光物质
and your photo bleaching.
照片也就不会因为荧光而褪色
- [Derek] So you're kind
of breaking it down?
所以你是希望荧光物质被分解？
- [Carl] So basically,
you're making the chemical
基本上就是要让这化学物质
not be able to function properly anymore.
不能够再发挥作用
What we found is the activity
levels changed significantly.
我们发现，蝎子的活跃程度有显著变化
So when you exposed to UV light,
当蝎子们受紫外线照射时
the non-fluorescence scorpions acted like
没有荧光的蝎子依然像
they were in the dark.
在黑暗中一样活动
There was no difference
between their behavior
它们的行为并无差异
and the dark and in UV light.
无论是处于黑暗还是紫外光下
Whereas when UV light
was present for the ones
然而，将荧光蝎子置于紫外灯下时
that can fluoresce, they
reduced their activity levels.
它们的活跃程度降低了
- [Derek] What's the conclusion from that?
从中能得到什么结论呢
- [Carl] The conclusion from that
结论就是
is that the fluorescents
itself is acting as a way to,
荧光本身作为一种方式
for them to detect the
presence of ultraviolet light.
被蝎子们用来探测紫外线
Another researcher by the
name of Douglas Gaffin,
另一个名叫 Douglas Gaffin 的研究者
came up with a great phrase for it.
给出了一个很合适的名字
I wish I'd come up with the
phrase, but I gotta give credit.
我真希望这是我想出来的，但我得承认这件事
He calls it, a whole-body photon detector.
他将其称为“全身光线探测器”
So it's part of their sensory system.
它是蝎子的感觉系统的一部分
What we don't know is why they want
我们还不知道，它们为什么如此渴望
to detect ultraviolet light so badly
探测到紫外光
that they've turned their whole
body into a photon detector.
以至于它们把整个身体都变成了光线探测器
The suspicion is that it
has to do with determining
我们怀疑这可能和
whether or not they
should come out at night.
是否要在夜间行动的决断有关
- [Derek] The idea is when UV light hits
按照这个想法，当紫外光照射到
a scorpion's body, it
fluoresces and the tail detects
蝎子的身体时，它就发出荧光，尾巴也会探测到
this emitted green light
alerting the scorpion
自身发出的绿光
that it is exposed so
it searches for cover.
警告它暴露了位置，要寻找藏身处
- [Carl] Scorpions are good at starving
蝎子很擅长挨饿
for long periods of time.
它们能撑很久
They don't need to eat that often.
不需要那么经常地进食
And coming out and foraging
is dangerous for them.
出来觅食对它们是很危险滴
And so they don't like to come out
所以它们也不喜欢
when it's a moonlit night.
在有月亮的夜间出来
Typically the only ones you'll
find out in the full moon
通常而言，你在月圆之夜能找到的仅有的蝎子
are the ones that are really
hungry, really need food.
是那些真的很饿，很需要食物的蝎子
If they're well fed, they'll stay down.
如果吃得很饱，它们会继续窝在地下
So they're using that
as basically their cue
总的来说，它们就用荧光作为环境信号
in the environment and saying, you know
这种信号表示
okay, this is how bright it is.
恩，外面似乎有点亮
So that's a cue as to how
likely I'm being preyed upon.
恐怕我已经被盯上了
And then here's how hungry I am.
可是现在又很饿
That's a cue how badly I need
to get out and get some food.
这又是一个信号，表明我有多么需要外出觅食
- [Derek] Right.
对
- [Dr. Carl] And then the
trade off between those two
而这两者的权衡
is basically should I go out tonight
大概就是，今晚是该出去
or should I stay in my hole.
还是留在洞里
- [Derek] Yeah.
是的
(techno sound)
- If you like overpaying
when you shop well,
then don't listen to this next part.
But if you want to save
money, then keep watching.
Because this portion of
the video is sponsored
by Capital One Shopping,
a free browser extension
that will automatically
find the best deals
when you shop online.
It's just two clicks
to install and it works
on all major browsers.
Then whenever you shop,
it'll work away in the background,
comparing prices and testing coupons
to make sure you never
overspend on an item again.
As much as I want to save money,
searching for bargains and
coupon codes is a big hassle
and Capital One Shopping
lets you get the best deals
without having to waste any of your time
finding those deals in the first place.
They all apply automatically at checkout.
They even have their own shopping page
that gathers products from
across different sites
and picks out the cheapest ones
so you can shop directly for
the best deals on the internet
and you don't need to be a
Capital One customer to use it.
This extension is free
for literally everyone.
So you can start saving money right away.
I want to thank Capital One Shopping
for sponsoring this portion of the video.
And I want to thank you for watching.